I live brother why are you still
grieving you were not the only thing I
lost I could have rebuilt you without
all that metal and left me a monster
like other creations that is a matter of
perspective you're hard to keep a scope
on Genji always so unpredictable oh I'm
sorry don't be it keeps me sharp
nice melody does he have a name
no sometimes I just hum when I'm
thinking I can stop huming or
thinking you haven't slept yeah was up
last night thinking about who we used to
be I try to focus on the good times hey
yeah we did have some of those I'd get a
biggest sword if I were you what counts
is the sharpness of the blade and the
mind of the wielder I said a bigger
sword not bigger words what did you do
you know before a crisis toara zenyata
if you don't mind me asking what did you
do before the crisis what was your
function before the crisis I collected
payments at a laser tag arena I was a
lifeguard at a water park I served
coffee I drove a tractor I massaged
sheep on a freerange pasture wait for
real is that
true is that true really could that be
seriously really he won't tell me
either I don't think so but he wouldn't
tell me either my cybernetic form came
at Great cost but you asked to change I
learned too young that my body couldn't
always keep up with me besides it's hard
to Turn Down rocket legs you cared too
much about the family perceived you have
you ever been the eldest son my brother
wasted too much of his life teaching you
I agree really yes like you I was
undeserving of his patience you do good
work with that blade when the path is
clear one walks with confidence this one
might get tricky can I count on you to
watch my back of course you are like a
brother to me you've told told me about
your family not sure that's a compliment
you have an adorable piece about you
things are simple when you protect the
innocent and when you meet the last done
innocent oh they get the Javin Genji
remember the time you tripped over your
sword in
training really that sounds like him ha
some Ninja no
way wish I was there
what
H is that
true is that true it only happened once
once was enough who taught you the blade
the best sword master in the
world master how do you maintain your
Tranquility amid endless battles I focus
on my breathing but you don't breathe
indeed remember when you had a bull cut
yes you didn't want to be the only one
one I never had one I believe I had
pictures it was not easy living in your
Shadow I would have preferred you at my
side what kind of armor polish do you
use anyway I make my own
with walnuts among other things he asks
if you have ever fought in an arena no I
have not he asks if you would like to if
you knew what black watch was up to why
didn't you stop them my vision was cled
by
and now the world pays for your actions
hindan we are the same Genji let's go to
the arcade after this a battle's end
calls for meditation not games I get it
everyone's scared to take on the best
player in the world fine I'll go so I'm
trying to ask everybody this what is
your favorite animal yeah Triceratops uh
yeah I can see it I have always been
bound to my duty now I have nothing
there is always a way to make something
from nothing
brother what a nauseating Bo of deja vu
yep working with you has always made me
sick are you planning to whine the whole
time
again I never knew you to be a showof
Genji only a fool wastes an opportunity
what are you wearing I could ask the
same of you Talon you are lucky I do not
cut you down where you
stand we would welcome the challenge
anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table I do not Swift
as the wind huh Genji even swifter
thanks to you you are as dangerous as
your storm that's nice of you to say I
think my sword and your Hammer will lead
us to Victory if you can't cut them nail
them I still feel that final Blow from
yesterday's training a come on I didn't
hit you that hard if that is the case
our enemies have much to fear